Shyen Wee.

• 7	U	•	•	•	

shyen.wee@gmail.com

github.com/fractalfeeling

Summary

+61 401453452

Analytical problem solver specialising in creative solutions, passionate about meaningful data and highly motivated by opportunities to fill gaps in existing processes with bespoke and novel solutions.

Driven self-starter learns through facing challenges head on, demonstrated previously in fast-paced high demand parliamentary role. Responsibilities included monitoring news flows and social media interactions, crafting time critical responses over a wide range of media.

Technical Programming Web Development **Management Systems** C, Python, SQL, Linux HTML5, CSS, Javascript Nationbuilder CRM/CMS, Moodle LMS Design e-Commerce Marketing Adobe Creative Suite Shopify and Wordpress Facebook Ad Manager and webstores email campaigns

Career

Electorate Officer - Parliament of Australia

Feb 2018-Jun 2019 / Kent Town, SA

- \rightarrow Analyse data from Facebook, Twitter and Nationbuilder providing insights to PR Director and Media Advisor for continuous improvement of social media content and delivery
- \rightarrow Optimise Facebook Ads using Lookalike Audiences and Customer Lifetime Value—achieving Facebook page follower growth of ~28% over 3 months
- \rightarrow Manage email campaigns—including weekly newsletter with donation appeal to \sim 80,000 people—achieving consistent open rate of 24-30% and bounce rate of <1% through email deliverability best practices, A/B testing and data validation on forms
- → Deliver election campaign material nationwide through SMS/MMS—over 1 million messages sent—with automated replies based on trigger keywords
- → Produce digital content consistent with brand and style guides and print collateral for election and fundraising campaigns compliant with AEC guidelines
- → Prepare financial reports of political donations and merchandise sales

IT & Technical Support Officer - Australian Institute of Technology Transfer

Apr 2011-Sep 2017 / Elizabeth, SA

- → Research and implement IT systems to increase productivity—implementations include setting up a local file server, router with security firmware for local WiFi management and digitisation of paper based feedback form system
- → Set up and manage Moodle student learning management system
- → Create documentation and train staff on Moodle LMS
- → Prepare reports from VETtrak data, compliant with AVETMISS reporting requirements
- → Provide technical support and maintenance of company IT assets

Projects / Volunteer

Student Mentor - 42 Adelaide

May-Jun 2022 / Adelaide, SA

- → Volunteer student mentor for the May 2022 Piscine—28-day school admission bootcamp
- \rightarrow Support prospective students on-campus and remotely, building on my past experiences to provide advice and guidance

Website Development and Marketing - Hanamura

April 2020 / Modbury, SA

- \rightarrow Build website with ordering and notification system to handle influx of online orders during the pandemic—hanamura.com.au
- ightarrow Generate Lookalike Audiences for ad targeting based on existing customer data
- → Optimise Facebook Ads for customer location

Education

42 Adelaide

Jan 2022-Present / Adelaide, SA